[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Characters, actions, places, occupations, and events in this series
are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Are you doing this to pressure me?
I have to protect our hotel’s interests.
This is my fault.
I’m the reason you are sick.
It’s your fault.
It’s all your fault, Key.
Everyone will die because of you.
Key used to have bad dreams when she was young.
Every time she has this dream, she always runs away.
Is there anything we can do to help Key?
I think we should call the police.
Yes.
Miss Key.
Hello, Key.
Where are you? Are you okay?
Peach.
Are you with Dad and Big Mom?
Yes, everyone is here.
Aunt Niam is also here.
Can you put me on speaker?
I want to talk to everyone.
Sure.
Key, where are you?
Are you safe?
I’m safe, Big Mom.
Honey, please come home.
Key, where are you?
Can you tell me?
Don’t worry about me.
I just need some time.
When I am stronger,
I will go back.
Okay.
Have you talked to Chan?
Peach.
Can you not tell Chan that I called?
I…
I don’t want her
to see me like this.
(Fine.)
If something happens, you need to call me immediately, alright?
Yes.
(The number you have dialed cannot be reached at the moment.)
This is the document for today’s meeting.
I can’t find Key.
I sent more people to look for her.
Thanks, Phu.
Don’t you have any place in mind
that she might be?
Game, cancel today’s meeting.
Yes.
Where are you going?
I’m going to look for Key.
Sun, can you take care of the hotel while I’m away?
I already assigned Game to take care of my work.
But if anything comes up, you can make the decision for me.
(Where are you going?)
I’m going to look for Key.
(Do you know where she is?)
I have a place in mind.
I’m going there to look for her.
(Alright. I’ll take care of the hotel.)
(You can go look for her.)
And…
Can you stop by to look after Simba?
(Sure.)
(Chan.)
(You need to find her…)
(and take her home.)
I’ll do everything to find her.
(Key, do you know this?)
(The moon and the stars,)
(we never see them clearly on the same night.)
Why?
If we can clearly see the stars like tonight,
it means that we won’t see the moon.
(On the night)
(that we can see the moon clearly,)
we won’t see the stars.
You’re right.
I can’t see the moon tonight.
Sometimes, we need to give something up
to keep something else alive.
(Key.)
(I know you probably don’t want to talk to me right now.)
If you hear this voice message,
I’m begging you.
(Please listen to the whole message.)
(I have something to tell you.)
(Simba and I,)
(we miss you very much.)
(Right now, I’m looking for you.)
(Even though I don’t know where you are,)
(I think you might be at the place where we first met.)
(Key, do you want to go watch the stars with me?)
(I want to go with you.)
(We need to go to a place far away and dark.)
(So we can clearly see the stars.)
(Key.)
(I forgot my phone in the car.)
(I’ll go get it and be right back.)
Mom, I’m scared.
Mom.
(The weather is cold.)
(I’ll put the blanket on you.)
(So you won’t get sick.)
(Mom.)
(Where are you, Mom?)
(I’m scared.)
(I’m really scared.)
(Mom killed herself because of you.)
(Because you came back.)
(Mom hated me because of you.)
(It’s all your fault, Key.)
(Because you came back.)
(Why did you come back?)
(Mom hated me because of you.)
(Everyone will die because of you.)
(Mom is dead because of you.)
(Mom is dead because of you, Key.)
(It’s all your fault.)
(Mom is dead because of you.)
(Everyone will die because of you.)
(It’s all your fault.)
(You killed Mom, Key.)
(Mom hated me because of you.)
(It’s all your fault, Key.)
(Because you came back.)
(Why did you come back?)
(Get out.)
(Get out. Why did you come back?)
(It’s your fault.)
(It’s all your fault, Key.)
(You killed Mom, Key.)
(You killed Mom.)
(Sometimes, we need to give something up)
(to keep something else alive.)
(Everyone will die because of you.)
(It’s all your fault.)
(Mom is dead because of you.)
(Everyone will die because of you.)
(Chan will die because of you.)
(Chan will die because of you. Everyone will die because of you.)
(Mom is dead because of you.)
Key.
I’m here. I’m right here.
It’s okay.
Key, look at me.
Look at me.
I’m here.
Sun.
Do you really want to see me?
Yes.
I haven’t seen you for a long time.
Because you are flying around.
You probably lose touch with all your friends.
What? This is my job.
If I didn’t fly, what else would I do?
Huh?
I saw you look stressed for a while.
What’s wrong?
It’s about my sister’s girlfriend.
What? Your twin has a new girlfriend?
Yes.
Didn’t you see the news?
No.
I don’t read entertainment gossip.
I don’t know your twin personally.
I have never met her.
Why?
Is her new girlfriend not a good person?
She’s nice.
I like her.
But the problem is my mom.
My mom doesn’t like her.
Wait.
You’ve complained to me about your sister’s girlfriends many times.
This is the first time that you said her girlfriend is okay.
Unlike when you talk about Jay,
you seem to really hate her.
Of course.
She did a terrible thing to my sister.
It’s hard not to hate her.
I now want to meet this girl, Jay.
Jay.
Wait, Jay.
Why don’t we go to another bar?
No. I’m going to drink here.
Do as you want.
Why are you following me?
I’m worried about you.
Why?
You are my friend.
How dare you come here?
I’m not in the mood to argue with you today.
Don’t be overreacting.
No, I’m not overreacting.
Backstabbing, that’s your style.
If you're talking about news about Key’s mom,
I didn’t do it.
Liar.
I said I didn’t do it.
I’m not that coward.
You may not be a coward.
But I think you are a loser.
Watch your mouth, girl.
Girls, stop it.
Calm down.
Sun.
Jay didn’t do it.
Whose side are you taking, Phu?
I’m not taking anyone’s side.
You, Chan, and Jay are my friends.
I just don’t want you guys to misunderstand each other.
Do you know that your mom asked me to steal Chan from Key?
But I refused to do it.
Because I have too much dignity to do that.
Jay is telling the truth.
She didn’t do it.
I can confirm that.
Your mom must think so poorly of Key.
She’d rather see me get back together with Chan.
Have you asked Chan
if she wants to take you back?
Calm down.
You are a celebrity.
You!
Long time no see.
Don’t get wasted today, Missy.
Elle.
Do you know her?
This is Jay, Chan’s ex?
Jay.
Jay, where are you going?
Now, I want to know about the news.
What happened?
Jay is the ex-girlfriend who dumped Chan.
But actually, she still loves Chan.
So she came back to Chan.
But Chan has already moved on.
She has a new girlfriend named Key.
Everything is heading toward a happy ending.
Suddenly, scandals about Key’s family explode.
So your mom doesn’t like her and wants them to break up.
She asks Jay to steal Chan from Key.
Right?
Your lives are so tangled.
Why can’t you do things the easy way?
Things should have been over if Jay didn’t come back.
Jay may not be a very nice person.
But I do feel sorry for her.
Why?
If I tell you, you will say I take her side.
Jay was guilt-tripped into breaking up with Chan
and marrying the American millionaire.
Jay’s aunt had a financial problem.
She was going to go bankrupt.
Marrying that man was the only way for her to save her family.
You are Phu, right?
I’m Elle.
Yes.
Can you do me a favor?
What do you want me to do?
Right.
What are you going to do?
I’m going to help you.
Thank you.
Are you feeling better?
It’s unbelievable
that you saved me both times.
How did you know
that I’m here?
I didn’t know.
But I had a hunch that you might be here.
This is the place where we first met.
That’s right.
This place,
it’s where I met you.
I thought…
this place might help me heal.
Why didn’t you tell me?
I could help you.
I didn’t want you…
to see me when I was falling apart.
So…
I ran away to be alone.
Tonight, the moon looks scary.
Some people believe that
a lunar eclipse is a bad sign.
But for me,
it’s just a natural phenomenon
when Earth casts a shadow on the Moon.
It won’t last long.
And it will pass.
Just like bad things that happened in the past,
in the end,
it will just be a thing of the past.
But I’m still afraid.
It’s dark.
I like it better when the moon shines brightly.
♪ There may be nights ♪
♪ when there’s no moon in the sky ♪
♪ Days when my heart feels far too tired to try ♪
♪ But somehow time led you into my life ♪
♪ You unlocked the empty space ♪
♪ and let me love you right ♪
♪ Feels just like a dream that I found you ♪
♪ Every second spent with you is so meaningful ♪
♪ The night shines bright, ♪
♪ no words could ever do ♪
♪ I know that it’s you ♪
♪ The word “love” I say to you, ♪
♪ I say it to you ♪
♪ You’re the shining light when no stars are coming through ♪
♪ You’re the key that found its way to my heart ♪
♪ Let me love you, love you ♪
Thank you for saving me.
So pretty.
Whose girlfriend is this?
Your girlfriend.
Chan.
You’re up?
Why didn’t you tell me?
I want to cuddle you a bit longer.
Doesn’t your arm hurt?
If it means I get to hold you,
it’s totally worth it.
This is more than cuddling.
Who did you learn this naughty behavior from?
Do you really need to ask that?
When you become close to someone,
you will pick up some of their behaviors.
That’s normal.
But I didn’t pick up any of your behaviors.
I guess we are not close enough.
Is this close enough?
Thank you
for holding me through the night.
I slept soundly and didn’t have any nightmares.
I will hold you any time you want.
Come on.
Let’s go home.
Right.
Simba must really miss me.
That’s true.
Let’s go home to our son.
I like what you said.
Why?
It’s like I have my own family.
There are Mama, Mommy, and our son, Simba.
Let’s hurry home.
Our son must be yowling nonstop.
Come on.
Thank you.
Sun.
What are you doing here, sweetie?
I came to help Chan with her work.
She’s busy.
You?
Yes, Mom.
I know the work process of our hotel.
She taught me in case something like this happens.
When did you learn it?
I never knew that you were interested in running our business.
Miss Sun doesn’t want Miss Chan to handle the hotel management alone.
She often came in to learn about the business when she had time.
That’s right.
These twins seem to really love each other.
Of course.
We are twins.
Whatever or whoever Chan loves, I will love them too.
Is that right?
But I’m her mom.
I love her and mean well to her.
There are some things that people your age might not have thought about.
I’m older. I should warn you about it, right?
Warning us out of concern and forcing us to do what you want,
these are two different things, Mom.
Are all kids these days such backtalkers?
Simba, where are you?
Mommy is back.
Do you miss me?
I’m sorry.
I’m back now.
Do you remember Mommy?
Are you mad at me?
Don’t leave your son again.
Simba, I’m not leaving you again.
Right?
Don’t leave Mama too.
Why have you never patted me on the head?
Why is this cat not meowing?
I’m a human.
Our family is warm.
Right?
Key.
Tonight,
let’s go to your family’s house.
Don’t worry.
I’ll always be by your side.
Hello, Aunt Niam.
Take off your shoes here.
Thank you.
Put the slippers on.
Hello.
I’m back.
I’m sorry that I worried you.
It’s alright, sweeties.
Just seeing you come back safely is good enough for me.
Thank you for taking her home.
You’re welcome.
Big Mom.
Dad.
Aunt Niam.
Yes.
This is Chan, my girlfriend.
Miss Key.
We’ve known it for some time.
We saw the news.
Miss Peach also told us
about your photoshoot celebrating your two-week anniversary of dating.
-You know all the details. -Of course.
This is an official introduction of her to my family.
Chan, do you know this?
There was a time when Key was young,
she went outside and watched the moon every night.
Sometimes, she fell asleep outside.
And you would carry me back to my bed every time.
Now, you have a girlfriend named Chan.
This must be destiny.
Key, honey.
Actually,
I have something to talk to you two about.
What is it?
Chan, do you know about Key’s mom and her and Key’s status in the family?
Dad.
I want you to know that
I’ve never thought less of Key.
I know.
But I want to explain so you two will understand.
Your mom loved you very much.
Because of her illness,
she did things that hurt you.
I know.
Every time she hurt me without meaning to,
she always regretted it.
I loved her.
I never hated her.
I know she was sick.
I was the one who made her condition worse.
It was my fault.
It was because of my incompetence.
I was secretly dating her
when we were in school.
My dad,
he forced me to marry Big Mom.
I did something selfish.
I hurt everyone.
Big Mom was really nice to me.
I never thought
that I would fall in love with her because of her goodness.
I ended up hurting your mom so badly
that she got ill.
I was a terrible man.
I couldn’t do anything…
to help your mom or you.
I’m sorry.
Dad.
You’re the best dad to me.
From now on,
you need to stop blaming yourself.
Do you hear me?
Thank you, Dad.
Chan.
Are we really going to sleep over here?
Yes.
Let’s sleep over here.
I want to see how you lived.
Key.
Yes.
Are you okay?
Let’s go.
You can’t sleep?
Yes.
Are you afraid?
I’m afraid that if I fall asleep,
I will have a nightmare about my mom.
I don’t want to see it again.
If you don’t want to have the nightmare again,
why don’t we face it together?
The doctor said that if I have someone I love,
it will help my healing.
I already have one. That’s you.
I don’t get why Chan loves Key that much.
That’s Chan’s business. It’s no longer yours.
Mom, are you going to sleep over here?
Why?
Are you going to tell me to leave again?
I’m not feeling well today.
I think I’m sick.
Do you want me to stay and take care of you?
If you have nothing else to do.
No problem, Mom.
Oops, I mean, Madam.
All we do is display our hatred to each other.
Don’t you feel bad for Chan?
Why do we have to hate each other?